{
    "id": "382e634eb4bf498bba01eb13fd35f6d3",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs With Carry",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "a9ccb4f4d9964a48b68370412e35def7",
            "title": "Phrasal Verbs With Carry",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "You will need a truck to .................................... all these books.",
                    "description": "To carry off is to transport.",
                    "answers": [
                        "carry off",
                        "carry on",
                        "carry over"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She .................................. her role really well.",
                    "description": "To carry off one's role is to act convincingly.",
                    "answers": [
                        "carried on",
                        "carried off",
                        "carried out"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Every year epidemics ................................ thousands of people.",
                    "description": "Carry off can mean cause death.",
                    "answers": [
                        "carry away",
                        "carry over",
                        "carry off"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She moved to the city to ................................ her work.",
                    "description": "To carry on something is to continue doing it.",
                    "answers": [
                        "carry over",
                        "carry out",
                        "carry on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "You cannot ............................. spending money like that if you do not want to end up in debt.",
                    "description": "To carry on something is to continue doing it.",
                    "answers": [
                        "carry off",
                        "carry through",
                        "carry on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "It is difficult to .............................. a conversation if you do not know the language.",
                    "description": "To carry on is to maintain.",
                    "answers": [
                        "carry out",
                        "carry with",
                        "carry on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "As my subordinate, your duty is to .............................. my instructions.",
                    "description": "To carry out is to fulfill.",
                    "answers": [
                        "carry with",
                        "carry through",
                        "carry out"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "They ................................ several experiments to prove their theory.",
                    "description": "To carry out is to do or perform.",
                    "answers": [
                        "carried on",
                        "carried out",
                        "carried over"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "His problems in his personal life,  ............................... to his work.",
                    "description": "If something carries over, it continues to exist.",
                    "answers": [
                        "carried out",
                        "carried over",
                        "carried through"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Though she was extremely tired, she ............................. to the finish.",
                    "description": "To carry something through is to finish it successfully.",
                    "answers": [
                        "carried out",
                        "carried over",
                        "carried through"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "We don't have enough supplies to carry us ............................ the winter.",
                    "description": "To carry someone through something is to help them survive a period of time.",
                    "answers": [
                        "over",
                        "through",
                        "off"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Her faith ................................. difficult times.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "carried her off",
                        "carried her away",
                        "carried her through"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}